#### Hello

#### I'm Emina Palamarevic

Email: minapala342@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://epalamarevic.github.io/Portfolio/portfolio.html

# **Objective**

For the past four years I have improved my professional skills in the healthcare field working as a patients service representative. I have developed relationships with patients, provided clerical duties in office and made an interest to expand my learning within IT. Eleven Fifty Academy has taught me the basics of software development. My professional goal is to use my skills in software development and healthcare to improve access to our future healthcare system.

#### **Education**

February 2020 - August 2020

Eleven Fifty Academy, Indianapolis – "Net Software Development Software Development Gold Badge Certificate Software Development Blue Badge Certificate Software Development Red Badge Certificate

August 2011 - May 2015

Indianapolis University Purdue University , Indianapolis *– Bachelor Science Health Service Management* 

## **Technology**

- Obtained HTML/CSS skills from web projects at Eleven Fifty Academy.
- Implemented back end components to utilize API. Net Framework with team members to develop an API.
- Conducted a full .Net Framework MVC project, using SQL, Javascript and Jquery.
- Made use of learning from applications such as; Virtual Studio, Postman, Github, Swagger.
- Use Epic application for patient records at Community Health Network.

## Leadership

- Improved organizational skills by multitasking; answering phones, greeting patients, checking patients in and out of the office at Community Health Network.
- Assisted in administrative projects as patient service representative.
- Practiced Relationship-Based Care with co-workers and students.
- Improved leadership skills by being part of the Shared Governance Council at Community Health Network.
- Managed thinking skills to complete multiple demands.
- Accomplished effective problem-solving with team building projects at Eleven Fifty Academy.
- Conducted agile project management methodology with the use of Trello during team projects at Eleven Fifty.

#### Communication

- Maintained positive communication within team members.
- Demonstrated flexibility in demanding work changes.
- Researched effectively to understand and learn new skills.
- Developed strong teamwork skills.
- Conducted conflict resolutions with errors within .Net projects.

## **Projects**

Flopify (.Net Framework API)

- Created a back-end API that uses C# code in relation to RESTful APIs.
- Used Swagger application to conduct and test the methods.
- Introduced XML representation in swagger.

GitHub: https://github.com/epalamarevic/Flopify/tree/master

Medical Billing Code (Full .Net Framework MVC)

- Full front-end and back-end development project; a website that shows a relation between IDC10 medical codes and pricing.
- Skills used are: C#, RESTful API, HTML, CSS, Javascript.

GitHub: https://github.com/epalamarevic/MedBillingCode

Azure: https://medicalbillingwebmvc20200727082839.azurewebsites.net

## **Experience**

November 2015 - PRESENT

Community Health Network, Indianapolis - Patient Service Representative

**Application Skills:** 

- EPIC
- OnBase
- Microsoft Word/Excel

January 2013 - May 2015

Indianapolis Marriott North, Indianapolis – *Room Server*